

PROFILE

I'm a frontend web developer with over 4 years' experience in software development.

Experienced in meeting client in collecting software requirement, leading teams, mentoring engineers and software architecture.

Agile development practice with html5, css3, JavaScript and cross-browser compatibility.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+841252181203 or 0394755263

WEBSITE:

https://okorochimezieportfolio1.netlify.app/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/mezieb

EMAIL:

Okorobright13@gmail.com

CURRENT LOCATION: Hanoi, Vietnam.

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Listening to music
- Swimming
- Meeting people

OKORO CHIMEZIE BRIGHT

Frontend Developer

EDUCATION

University of Nigeria Nuskka, UNN.

2007 - 2011

Mathematics (B.Sc./Ed).

FPT University, Hanoi, Vietnam.

015 - 2017

Software Engineering (M, SE). Area of specialization data analytic.

WORK EXPERIENCE

IGHOLINK SYSTEMS TECHOLOGIES NIGERIA Data Analyst

2011-2014

Cong ty co phan ANTI-Antti GROUP VIETNAM Sales rep

2016-2019

I work as a data analyst, sales rep, team leader, I helped the company to achieve international certificate of partnership innovative programme between Finland and Vietnam.

Freelancer Frontend Developer

2019-till date

I help you design your ideal website from simple to complex, with a business solution that suit your business needs in phases. Feel free to visit my portfolio and GitHub.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- 1: HTML5
- 2: CSS3
- 3: JAVASCRIPT
- 4: REACT JS
- 5: BOOTSTRAP
- 6: GITHUB